## **Victor Queiroz**

victornqueiroz@gmail.com +81 080 8011 7167 〒158-0092 Tokyo, Setagaya-ku, Noge 1-9-3 Maison do Ash 101

Overview

Ambitious product manager with 10 years experience and passionate about building products from ideation to release. Experienced in working with different areas, such as engineering, marketing and design. Able to manage stakeholders expectations, sharing plans and presenting results.

Skills

Project Management, Agile Development, Scrum, Jira, Figma, User Experience Design, Adobe Suite, Final Cut Pro

Experience

Wahl+Case - May 2021 - Present

Marketing, Creative Specialist - Tokyo, Japan

- Planning and executing solutions to increase candidate acquisition and conversion;
- Leading marketing initiatives to promote brand awareness and interaction on Social Media by art directing and producing all kinds of media contents;

Attuned.ai – August 2018 - May 2021 Head of Product - Tokyo, Japan

- Led the development of a SaaS product that uses science-backed data and AI to help companies build happier and more productive workplaces;
- Designed innovative solutions to display complex data to managers, helping them making better decisions in their own teams;
- Managed teams in Vietnam and Japan;

Justa – March 2017 - August 2018 Head of Product - Tokyo, Japan

- Directed the development of the biggest job board for startups in Japan;
- Grew the user base from 10,000 to 25,000 users in a year;
- Managed a team of 3 developers, 2 sales and 1 marketer;

Linte – 2016 - 2017 COO - São Paulo, Brazil

- Created a cloud-based software that helps companies lowering expenses in litigation management;
- Hired and managed a team that grew from 2 to 10 people in a year;

VaiVolta - 2014 - 2016

Founder, COO - São Paulo, Brazil / Mountain View, United States

- Founded the company, growing to 15,000 clients in 2 years;
- Raised investment for the company and was selected to join the acceleration program of 500 Startups in California;

Education

Degree in System Analysis and Development, UNICAMP - 2011 Learned programming languages including C/C++, Java, Javascript, MySQL.

About

Tokyo based. Born in Brazil, lived in Belgium, UK, Unites States and Japan. Speaks English, Portuguese, French and Japanese. Living in Japan since 2016.